[
  {
    "question": "friend",
    "answer": "друг",
    "category": "#english",
    "id": "english_0"
  },
  {
    "question": "dog",
    "answer": "собака",
    "category": "#english",
    "id": "english_1"
  },
  {
    "question": "cat",
    "answer": "кошка",
    "category": "#english",
    "id": "english_2"
  },
  {
    "question": "house",
    "answer": "дом",
    "category": "#english",
    "id": "english_3"
  },
  {
    "question": "book",
    "answer": "книга",
    "category": "#english",
    "id": "english_4"
  },
  {
    "question": "tree",
    "answer": "дерево",
    "category": "#english",
    "id": "english_5"
  },
  {
    "question": "sun",
    "answer": "солнце",
    "category": "#english",
    "id": "english_6"
  },
  {
    "question": "water",
    "answer": "вода",
    "category": "#english",
    "id": "english_7"
  },
  {
    "question": "food",
    "answer": "еда",
    "category": "#english",
    "id": "english_8"
  },
  {
    "question": "car",
    "answer": "машина",
    "category": "#english",
    "id": "english_9"
  },
  {
    "question": "amigo",
    "answer": "друг",
    "category": "#spanish",
    "id": "spanish_0"
  },
  {
    "question": "perro",
    "answer": "собака",
    "category": "#spanish",
    "id": "spanish_1"
  },
  {
    "question": "gato",
    "answer": "кошка",
    "category": "#spanish",
    "id": "spanish_2"
  },
  {
    "question": "casa",
    "answer": "дом",
    "category": "#spanish",
    "id": "spanish_3"
  },
  {
    "question": "libro",
    "answer": "книга",
    "category": "#spanish",
    "id": "spanish_4"
  },
  {
    "question": "árbol",
    "answer": "дерево",
    "category": "#spanish",
    "id": "spanish_5"
  },
  {
    "question": "sol",
    "answer": "солнце",
    "category": "#spanish",
    "id": "spanish_6"
  },
  {
    "question": "agua",
    "answer": "вода",
    "category": "#spanish",
    "id": "spanish_7"
  },
  {
    "question": "comida",
    "answer": "еда",
    "category": "#spanish",
    "id": "spanish_8"
  },
  {
    "question": "coche",
    "answer": "машина",
    "category": "#spanish",
    "id": "spanish_9"
  },
  {
    "question": "ami",
    "answer": "друг",
    "category": "#french",
    "id": "french_0"
  },
  {
    "question": "chien",
    "answer": "собака",
    "category": "#french",
    "id": "french_1"
  },
  {
    "question": "chat",
    "answer": "кошка",
    "category": "#french",
    "id": "french_2"
  },
  {
    "question": "maison",
    "answer": "дом",
    "category": "#french",
    "id": "french_3"
  },
  {
    "question": "livre",
    "answer": "книга",
    "category": "#french",
    "id": "french_4"
  },
  {
    "question": "arbre",
    "answer": "дерево",
    "category": "#french",
    "id": "french_5"
  },
  {
    "question": "soleil",
    "answer": "солнце",
    "category": "#french",
    "id": "french_6"
  },
  {
    "question": "eau",
    "answer": "вода",
    "category": "#french",
    "id": "french_7"
  },
  {
    "question": "nourriture",
    "answer": "еда",
    "category": "#french",
    "id": "french_8"
  },
  {
    "question": "voiture",
    "answer": "машина",
    "category": "#french",
    "id": "french_9"
  }
]
